Wilkin Amador

6653 Belle Shadow Lane, Tampa FL 33634 | 978-885-5531 | wilkinanthony94@gmail.com

PROFILE:

FAA certified Airframe and Powerplant mechanic with experience in aviation structures, composites, and MROs

CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS:

FAA Airframe & FAA Powerplant License A320, B757, B767, B737 Gen Fams Forklift Certified GMM Training Scissor lift/Boom lift Operator CAT Qualified

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

A&P Mechanic 05/2023 - Current

United Airlines | Tampa, FL

• Responsible for replacing or repairing various components throughout the aircraft including landing gear, APU, hydraulics, engine, cabin, and avionics systems

A&P Mechanic 04/2022-05/2023

FEAM | Lakeland, FL

- Preformed aircraft maintenance on Boeing 767 aircraft
- Documented logbook entries and utilized Maintenix system
- Serviced landing gear as well as various types of line maintenance duties
- Utilized aircraft maintenance manuals and Complied with ADs and Service Bulletins per FAA regulations

A&P Mechanic 09/2021-04/2022

STS Line Maintenance | Orlando, FL

- Preformed routine and non-routine aircraft maintenance on Frontier's A319's, A320's, and A321's
- Serviced landing gear as well as various types of line maintenance duties

A&P Mechanic 02/2021-09/2021

Airborne MX | Tampa, FL

- Responsible for servicing landing gears doors, mount engines, common nozzles assemblies (CNA's), exhaust
 cones, exhaust ducts, service rudders, flaps, elevators, ailerons, engine inlets, heat exchangers, ozone filters, and
 brakes on A320 and B737
- Performed inspections on engine mounts and bolts

Composite Technician 10/2020-02/2021

Aeromatrix Composites | Clearwater, FL

- Contributed to the payloads operation using carbon fiber material to form flare canisters for military aircraft.
- Utilized mandrel sets, mold assemblies, and ovens to cure materials
- Set up interior panels for Sikorsky helicopters using various tools including routers, sanding blocks, pneumatic tools, and grinders

Structures Mechanic 01/2020-9/2020

Piper Aircraft | Vero Beach, FL

- Performed Malibu fuselage assembly of 350, 500, 600s, and archer aircraft
- Assigned to the aft cabins team before the final assembly was completed
- Utilized drills, rivet presses, bucking bars, scales, rivet guns, cherry max guns, shear cutters, and tin snips

EDUCATION:

Diploma, Aviation Maintenance Technology

05/2018-10/2019

National Aviation Academy (FAA Part 147) | Concord, MA

Diploma

Greater Lawrence Vocational Tech | Andover, MA